Dhananjaya Maha Malage

Chief Technology Officer (CTO) - Colombo, Sri Lanka

+94715395051

✓ dhanmalage@gmail.com

in Linkedin

Github

Stackoverflow

Personal Profile

I am a multidisciplinary solution architect. I help people translate ideas from words and visuals into prototypes and applications using code that help organizations address business challenges and meet their needs. Having been involved in both collaborative and independently-driven roles, I am a forward-thinking leader with refined analytical and critical thinking skills, and I have always been adapting myself to meet evolving priorities, shifting needs, and emergent issues. I have deep experience in translating business priorities to IT roadmaps and fine-tuned IT operating models.

Education

University of Colombo School of Computing (UCSC)

Bachelor of Information Technology

Colombo, Sri Lanka

Experience

Chief Technology Officer

J. Arthur & Co.

Technical Lead

J. Arthur & Co.

Technical LeadOSMiUM Private Ltd

Senior Web Application Engineer

Suxiid Private Ltd

Solution ArchitectSelf Employed (Freelance)

2013 - 2019

Newport, USA (remote) 2019 - PRESENT

Newport, USA (remote)

2017 - 2019

Colombo, Sri Lanka

2018 - 2019

Colombo, Sri Lanka

2014 - 2018

Colombo, Sri Lanka 2014 - PRESENT

Technical Skills

Languages: PHP, Javascript, SQL, Dart, Python

MVC Frameworks: Laravel, Codeigniter

Frontend Frameworks: VueJS, React, Bootstrap

Mobile Applications: Flutter

Databases: Postgres, MySQL & MongoDB

CMS: Wordpress Theme/Plugin Development

Web Servers: Apache, Ngnix, IIS

OS: Linux, Windows

Virtualization: Vagrant, VirtualBox Other: NodeJS, HTML, CSS, jQuery